{"data":[{"question":"The customer was interested see one of those new pocket cameras with the built-in flash.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"see","c":"those","d":"the built-in","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- See-> in seeing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"My teacher said we should write another composition for tomorrow related for our experience at last week's workshop.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"should write","b":"related for","c":"at","d":"week's","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Related for-> related to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The jury be trying to reach a decision.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"be","c":"to","d":"reach","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Be->is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Of the two landscape that you have shown me, this one is the more picturesque.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Of the two landscape","b":"that","c":"me","d":"the more","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- The more->more","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Linh didn't lose any time in applying for the teaching position on math.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"lose","b":"in applying","c":"the teaching","d":"on math","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- on-> of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"When the roads became too slippery, we decided to return to the cabin and wait for the storm to subsiding.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"too slippery","b":"to return","c":"wait for","d":"subsiding","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Subsiding-> subside","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"When teenagers finish high school, they have several choices; going to college, getting a job or the army.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"teenagers","b":"several choices","c":"going to","d":"the army","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- The army-> joining the army","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Teachers whom do not spend enough time on class preparation often have difficulty in explaining new lessons.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"whom","b":"enough time","c":"class preparation","d":"explaining new lessons","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Whom-> who","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The hotel was such very noise that they couldn't sleep.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The hotel","b":"such very noise","c":"that","d":"couldn't sleep","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Such-> so","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Get on the bus outside the station, and get them off at Park street.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Get on","b":"outside","c":"get them off","d":"at","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Get them off-> get off","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"}]}